KRISTY KELLER

Philadelphia, PA | Phone: (570)955-7724 | Email: keller.kristy@outlook.com | Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/kellerkristy/ | GitHub: https://github.com/KristyKeller | Portfolio: https://kristy-keller-portfolio.herokuapp.com

SUMMARY

Full-Stack Web Development • Testing • Web Design • Product Management • Content Writing • eCommerce

Adaptable, detail-oriented full-stack web developer with experience applying social coding, refactoring and debugging code, building and designing content, creating front end and back end websites, and executing problem solving with testing. My super power is proactive learning and teamwork, combining precision with creativity.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Adobe Creative Suite, Adobe Photoshop, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Handelbars.js, JSON, Javascript, JQuery, Web (REST) API's, React, Node.js, Express, Microsoft Office Suite, MySQL, MongoDB

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

eCommerce Content Specialist DICK'S Sporting Goods

November 2017 – July 2020 Pittsburgh, PA

Drove online traffic, conversion and revenue while maintaining a brand voice for apparel product display pages. Trained and presented processes and results to various levels of the organization and vendors, and incorporated customer feedback to improve and enhance web experience.

Key Accomplishments:

- Increased Outdoor Apparel 2019 demand sales by +17% through collaborating with vendors for enhanced assets
- Lead the 2018 enhanced outwear photo shoot, heightening product display pages for key assortments
- Promoted to key content product manager for Nike, a key partner
- Tested and updated over 5,000 outdated product display pages to HTML5 and added cleaner description design, receiving positive customer and managerial feedback

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

Freelance Content Writer Skyword, Inc.

August 2016 – July 2019 Remote

Disney College Program Cast Member Walt Disney World

January 2016 – May 2016 Orlando, FL

International Digital Marketing Intern Sodexo, Inc.

June 2015 – July 2015 Madrid, Spain

PROJECTS

Team Generator | https://github.com/KristyKeller/TeamGenerator | https://rebrand.ly/generator-demo

- Software engineering team generator command line application. When the user has completed building the team, the application creates an HTML file that displays a formatted team roster
- Built front-end with HTML and CSS, Express for routing
- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Jest.js testing, Node.js, Express.js, Github API, CLI application

Stream Saver | https://github.com/KristyKeller/Stream-Saver | https://stream-saver.herokuapp.com

- An application that lets the user search, mark watched, and save to a watch list any show or movie they'd like to stream once they sign into their account
- Served as the team manager, built all front-end skeletons with Handlebars.js and HTML, added functionality to front-end using JQuery, and tested search results, fixing search errors
- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, Handlebars.is, MySQL, JavaScript, API, Node.js

Ice Cream ORM | https://github.com/KristyKeller/IceCreamTruck | https://ice-cream-truck.herokuapp.com/

- Ice cream logger app that lets users order ice cream flavors to be devoured, storing all orders in a database, whether devoured or not
- Designed front-end with HTML and CSS while using Express for routing and MySQL to create and query a
 database
- HTML5, Handlebars.js, CSS3, JavaScript, Homemade ORM, Node.js, Express, MySQL

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Development Certificate: University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, PA Master of Business Administration: Point Park University, Pittsburgh, PA Master of Arts, Media Communication: Point Park University, Pittsburgh, PA Bachelor of Arts, Communication: Keystone College, La Plume, PA